The Complete Wonsulting Resume Guide!

Follow these steps to land your dream job

- 1. Create your resume with our popular resume template (page 2)
- 3. Master your job search with our online job search course
- •• Or save time and build confidence with <u>1-on-1 guidance</u>! Our recruiters & hiring managers will help you plan your career and conquer your interviews!

90% of our clients land interviews within 3 months and 70% get job offers within 6 months

Extra Resources! Fix your resume with these videos:

The Complete Resume Guide	How To Write a Resume with No Job Experience	<u>3 Biggest Resume</u> <u>Mistakes</u>	The Truth About Applicant Tracking System (ATS)
THE COMPLETE RESUME OULDS	Continue Complete A RESUME	RESUME MIST AKES	THE TRUTH ABOUT APPLICANT TRACKING SYSTEMS

More Videos: <u>Subscribe to Wonsulting on YouTube</u>
Watch Now: <u>Can an Al Generated Resume Land an Interview at FAANG?</u>

<u>Jonathan's IG</u> <u>Jerry's IG</u>

Resume Examples

<u>Jonathan (Student)</u> <u>Jerry (Student)</u> <u>Jonathan (Professional)</u> <u>Jerry (Professional)</u>

Follow us below 😄















LinkedIn

Instagram

Tik Tok

<u>YouTube</u>

Twitter

Pinterest

Ouora

Keith Black

Atlanta, GA | www.linkedin/keith-black-developer | 312-493-1781 | keithblack@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Digital Crafts Atlanta, GA

Web Development Cohort

Feb. 2023-June 2023

DePaul University

Chicago, IL

Accounting and Finance/BS

Aug. 2008

WEB DEVELOPMENT EXPERIENCE

DIGITAL CRAFTS

Atlanta, GA

Web Development Cohort

Feb. 2018 - Jan. 2022

• Learned practical skills and current technologies in a hands-on immersive course.

•

WORK EXPERIENCE

E*TRADE

Alpharetta, GA

Senior Stock Plan Specialist

Feb. 2018 - Jan. 2022

- Provided high touch service to stock plan participants and took ownership of customer issues
- Thrived in fast-paced, detail-oriented environment to achieve outstanding performance and efficiency metrics
- Brokered trades for clients
- Supported clients through inbound, outbound calls, and secure messages
- Acted as a liaison with employee stock plan participants.
- Provided education on stock plan awards such as stock options, restricted shares, and ESPP plans.
- Brokered transactions involving equity awards and explained tax implications.
- Formulated and delivered solutions for participant inquiries, ranging from foundational guidance to more complex product-related questions.
- Engaged with clients across the participant lifecycle, introducing additional wealth and liquidity solutions where appropriate.

TradeStation Securities

Chicago, IL

Senior Account Executive/Broker

2012 - 2016

- Utilized exceptional sales skills & articulation of company value to acquire new brokerage clients through multiple sales channels.
- Obtained numerous high revenue generating VIP clients and maintained long term relationships.
- To make your resume flow, read it over. Check and see if it is easy to read with no overflowing of text. You should avoid the usage of different colors, multiple fonts, pictures, and brief/too dense information. Your resume should show who you are while being professional.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

 JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Jest, Supertest

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATIONS

- Microsoft Certified Systems Engineer (MCSE)
- FINRA Series 7, 3, 63
- Certified Equity Professional (Santa Clara University)

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Skills: Financial markets and analysis, portfolio construction.

Interests: Artificial Intelligence, Fintech, maintaining efficient and maintainable code

PASSIONS

Financial literacy, economics, senior care and wellbeing,

Resume Example [Professional]

Location | LinkedIn | Phone Number | Email

WORK EXPERIENCE

Company
Position

Location
Dates

- This section regarding experiences has bulleted accomplishments, which provide examples of when you successfully used the skills employers are seeking. Make sure you have between 2 and 5 bullet points in each section.
- Your bullet points should start with a strong action verb, which then follows with an explanation of
 what you were doing, describe how you did it, and most importantly if applicable, any achievements.
 Statements should convey your strengths/proficiencies in one or more skills that intrigue the employer
 by showing examples of when you have used them.
- When writing about your experience, consider these questions: What was the result/outcome of your work? What were your accomplishments? How did you impact the organization? What skills/knowledge did you grow? How does this experience relate to your internship/employment goal?

CompanyPosition

Location
Dates

- Your bullet statements should be in proper tense, using –ed for past experiences and present tenses for current positions. Make sure that your writing is free of grammatical errors and punctuation.
- When including numerical achievements during your experiences, make sure to include (if applicable) the quantity, population, frequency, and impact of your work whenever possible.
- To make your resume flow, read it over. Check and see if it is easy to read with no overflowing of text. You should avoid the usage of different colors, multiple fonts, pictures, and brief/too dense information. Your resume should show who you are while being professional.

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

Company
Position
Location
Dates

- This section is optional if you have various leadership experiences and other activities you want employers to know. By having multiple sections, it allows you to emphasize your most relevant experience.
- Positions within this section should be formatted similar to previous experience sections, including bullet points if necessary.
- You may also include work experiences that may not be directly related to the job/internship you are applying to, but add to your credibility by exemplifying your past work experiences.

EDUCATION

University Location

*Major/Degree*GPA, Organizations, Coursework, etc.

Graduation Date

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Skills: These skills should be concrete and testable. These should not be soft skills like communication, organizational, and interpersonal skills, but instead incorporated into your bulleted accomplishment statements above. You can add technology skills (Ex: Microsoft Office, Quickbooks, SQL, etc.) and languages (Ex: Spanish, French)

Interests: What are you interested in getting into + what do you like to do outside of work/for fun?

Wonsulting Wendy [Student]

Los Angeles, CA | LinkedIn | 562-111-1111 | hello@wonsulting.com

EDUCATION

San Jose State University

San Jose, CA

BS in Business Administration, Marketing (GPA: 3.9)

Graduation Date: June 2020

Organizations/Awards: Honors Program, Second Harvest, Dean's Honors List, Chancellor's Honors List

WORK EXPERIENCE

Wonsulting

Los Angeles, CA

Marketing Strategist

September 2020 – Present

- Generate reports on Sprout Social and Excel to conduct trend analysis for social media content, identifying niche to optimize organic reach from 13% to 27% in a span of 3 months.
- Collaborate with senior management including marketing lead to grow Instagram and LinkedIn accounts, implementing posting schedules for popular content which increased followers to 100k+
- Provide recommendations to enter a niche market for career tips, conducting market research on Qualtrics for 100+ infographics and video content on TikTok
- Utilize CRM platforms including Salesforce and Hubspot to service 50+ clients daily, working with sales team to identify pain points and marketing opportunities for success stories

Target San Jose, CA

Sales Manager

January 2019 - January 2020

- Analyzed financial statements, business summary reports, and dashboard recaps to attain data based on product comparable percentages and penetration rates for district managers which increased store efficiency by 16%.
- Collaborated with senior management on multiple functions including customer success and finance, increasing survey submissions from 60% previous month to 75% by identifying the pain points of customer feedback.
- Evaluated 100+ employees in 6 departments through surveys and office hours assessing strengths and overall skills which improved productivity for tasks by 23% daily.

Nordstrom San Francisco, CA

Seasonal Sales Associate

April 2018 – September 2018

- Presented recommendations for seasonal sales items including clothing and electronics to senior management, streamlining POS which accumulated to \$1,500 in sales daily
- Reviewed P&L with sales lead and district manager to identify highest & lowest penetration rates on all products, analyzing all products which increased efficiency of deliveries from store to customer by 17%
- Maintained and built relationships with 100+ customers daily, providing exceptional customer service and efficient product deliveries daily which translated to a customer satisfaction rating score of 97%

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

Association of Latino Professionals For America (ALPFA)

Riverside, CA

Director of Professional Development

April 2017 – Present

• Partner with 100+ professionals and recruiters in various firms and organizations, bringing out 10+ companies including Deloitte, KPMG, Vanguard, and Kohl's for our Professional Networking Dinner with 150+ attendees.

Spearhead events for weekly meetings regarding resumes, cover letters, and LinkedIn workshops, presenting research during ALPFA Regional, Los Angeles Pre-Convention workshop for 110+ students and professionals.

Second Harvest Toronto, ON

Volunteer Lead

March 2019 – May 2019

- Coordinated 3 events with team members regarding food rescue charities at local businesses, generating 50 tons of vegetables and fruits to donate to 500+ homeless shelters across the Toronto area
- Provided 105+ vegetable meals daily to front-line workers to help prevent 70M+ pounds of greenhouse gasses

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Skills: Microsoft Office (Excel, PowerPoint) | Sprout Social | Salesforce | HubSpot | Qualtrics | CRM Interests: Marketing & Operations, Analytics, Career Consulting, Speaking at Universities, Basketball

Wonsulting Wendy [Professional]

Los Angeles, CA | LinkedIn | 562-111-1111 | hello@wonsulting.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Wonsulting Los Angeles, CA

Marketing Strategist

September 2020 – Present

- Generate reports on Sprout Social and Excel to conduct trend analysis for social media content, identifying niche to optimize organic reach from 13% to 27% in a span of 3 months.
- Collaborate with senior management including marketing lead to grow Instagram and LinkedIn accounts, implementing posting schedules for popular content which increased followers to 100k+
- Provide recommendations to enter a niche market for career tips, conducting market research on Qualtrics for 100+ infographics and video content on TikTok
- Utilize CRM platforms including Salesforce and Hubspot to service 50+ clients daily, working with sales team to identify pain points and marketing opportunities for success stories

Target San Jose, CA

Sales Manager

January 2019 - January 2020

- Analyzed financial statements, business summary reports, and dashboard recaps to attain data based on product comparable percentages and penetration rates for district managers which increased store efficiency by 16%.
- Collaborated with senior management on multiple functions including customer success and finance, increasing survey submissions from 60% previous month to 75% by identifying the pain points of customer feedback.
- Evaluated 100+ employees in 6 departments through surveys and office hours assessing strengths and overall skills which improved productivity for tasks by 23% daily.

Nordstrom San Francisco, CA

Seasonal Sales Associate

April 2018 – September 2018

- Presented recommendations for seasonal sales items including clothing and electronics to senior management, streamlining POS which accumulated to \$1,500 in sales daily
- Reviewed P&L with sales lead and district manager to identify highest & lowest penetration rates on all products, analyzing all products which increased efficiency of deliveries from store to customer by 17%
- Maintained and built relationships with 100+ customers daily, providing exceptional customer service and efficient product deliveries daily which translated to a customer satisfaction rating score of 97%

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

Association of Latino Professionals For America (ALPFA)

Riverside, CA

Director of Professional Development

April 2017 – Present

- Partner with 100+ professionals and recruiters in various firms and organizations, bringing out 10+ companies including Deloitte, KPMG, Vanguard, and Kohl's for our Professional Networking Dinner with 150+ attendees.
- Spearhead events for weekly meetings regarding resumes, cover letters, and LinkedIn workshops, presenting research during ALPFA Regional, Los Angeles Pre-Convention workshop for 110+ students and professionals.

Second Harvest Toronto, ON March 2019 - May 2019

Volunteer Lead

- Coordinated 3 events with team members regarding food rescue charities at local businesses, generating 50 tons of vegetables and fruits to donate to 500+ homeless shelters across the Toronto area
- Provided 105+ vegetable meals daily to front-line workers to help prevent 70M+ pounds of greenhouse gasses

EDUCATION

San Jose State University

San Jose, CA

BS in Business Administration, Marketing (GPA: 3.9)

Graduation Date: June 2020

• Organizations/Awards: Honors Program, Second Harvest, Dean's Honors List, Chancellor's Honors List

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Skills: Microsoft Office (Excel, PowerPoint) | Sprout Social | Salesforce | HubSpot | Qualtrics | CRM

Interests: Marketing & Operations, Analytics, Career Consulting, Speaking at Universities, Basketball